Family is family. Blood is blood.
Cassandra's Dream is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Woody Allen.
The tale of two brothers with serious financial woes.
When a third party proposes they turn to crime,
things go bad and the two become enemies.
Terry Blaine, played by Colin Farrell.
Ian Blaine, played by Ewan McGregor.
Angela, played by Hayley Atwell.
Kate, played by Sally Hawkins.
Howard, played by Tom Wilkinson.
Martin Burns, played by Phil Davis.
Cassandra's Dream is a 2007 crime thriller drama film
written and directed by Woody Allen.
It stars Hayley Atwell, Colin Farrell, Sally
Hawkins, Ewan McGregor and Tom Wilkinson.
Shot in England, the film is a co-production between the
United States, France, and the United Kingdom.
The film premiered in secret in Avilés, Spain, on 18 June 2007.
It officially premiered at the 64th Venice International Film Festival on 2
September 2007 and was already in theaters in Spain by 3 November.
The film had its North American premiere at the Toronto
International Film Festival on 11 September 2007.
Cassandra's Dream was released theatrically in France on 31 October 2007, in the United
States on 18 January 2008, and in the United Kingdom on 23 May 2008.
The film explores themes of sailboat, sibling relationship, love
triangle, restart, parent child relationship.
The tone is emotional and intense.